{
    "subject": "Barbara_Rush",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jeffrey_Hunter",
    "human_readable": "Barbara Rush is married to Jeffrey Hunter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9655395746231079,
            "question": "When did Barbara Rush and Jeffrey Hunter get married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8823832869529724,
            "question": "Who is Barbara Rush married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8383190035820007,
            "question": "Who was Jeffrey Hunter married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7045178413391113,
            "question": "Do Barbara Rush and Jeffrey Hunter have any children together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6257907748222351,
            "question": "Is Barbara Rush in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5592854022979736,
            "question": "What is the name of Jeffrey Hunter's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5335203409194946,
            "question": "Where did Barbara Rush and Jeffrey Hunter meet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5241907835006714,
            "question": "Are Barbara Rush and Jeffrey Hunter known for being actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26986372470855713,
            "question": "What are some of Barbara Rush's notable roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23773987591266632,
            "question": "What is Jeffrey Hunter best known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Barbara Rush is married to Jeffrey Hunter.",
            "html": "yago_25248_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Barbara Rush's notable roles?",
            "html": "yago_25248_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Barbara Rush and Jeffrey Hunter known for being actors?",
            "html": "yago_25248_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Barbara Rush and Jeffrey Hunter meet?",
            "html": "yago_25248_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25248_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances that support the statement \"Barbara Rush is married to Jeffrey Hunter.\" These include direct mentions of their marriage in various years and details about their son, Christopher."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}